Truly all these images are made out of relationship and couldn't be made otherwise.
The other piece I'm thinking about is that little sort of cartoony image I made with
Sins and Valid during one of the Sultangaza. It says disability justice means resisting together
from solitary cells to open air prisons to exist is to resist. There's so much devastation here but
that's not what you see you see the hands. Right and the good is truly the goal and hope of my
work is to be in service and solidarity and love with the people who are most targeted by these
systems. So then because they have taught me so much. You know as I just worked there there are many
times when also I've had to confront the ways that I really haven't shown up for other oppressed
communities that are so close to me, you know, including intersex folks, including other disabled
after I became more disabled. I of course sadly went back and started understanding all my work
through a disability justice lens. And so this image was a rapid response piece. It was made by
myself in Paddyburn because we're family and just hanging out her house when I talking about,
you know, how hard broken and outrage we are about the genocide in Gaza and the way that Gaza is
an open air prison and the the ways that our police forces and military are intertwined with that
apartheid state and the ways that all of these carceral systems are disabling. Then I see that many
people use it in an academic setting and serve to talk about these these big concepts
of connecting abolition to colonization apartheid and militarization. So this I think this is another one
that I'm proud of.